Guide to the National Education Association-Committees records, 1857-1996 NEA1003.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Committee on Professional Ethics, 1903-1983; 1960-1975; Series 6; 20.5 Linear Feet
  - Investigations-Holwell, James F. (Roosevelt, NY), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1209, Folder 14)
  - Investigations-Hopkins, Everett (Arvada, CO), 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 1209, Folder 15)
  - Investigations-Hughes, Elogene C. (West Babylon, NY), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1209, Folder 16)
  - Investigations-Hunter, Roy Lee (Unadilla, GA), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1209, Folder 17)
  - Investigations-Jervey, Edward (Radford, VA), 1968-1973; Series 6 (Box 1209, Folder 18)
  - Investigations-Johnson, Dan (Greenville, TN), 1964; Series 6 (Box 1209, Folder 19)
  - Investigations-Johnson, Leslie W. (Sheboygan, WI), 1958-1963; Series 6 (Box 1209, Folder 20)
  - Investigations-Johnson, William H. (Chicago, IL), 1945-1946; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Jolley, Judith Ann (Roy, UT), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Joplin Community Teachers Association [file 1/2], 1970-1971; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Joplin Community Teachers Association [file 2/2], 1970-1971; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Jordan School District (Midvale, UT), 1962-1963; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Julius, Robert J. (Sturgis, SD), 1968-1970; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Kane, Julian (Great Neck, NY), 1967-1969; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Kane, Merville (Waukegan, IL), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Keene, John F. (Farmingdale, NY), 1964-1966; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Kellerman, George (Roosevelt, NY), 1961; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-King Fisher County, OK, 1965; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Kleinman, Sidney C. (Chicago, IL), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1210, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Knoxville Teachers League, 1966-1969; Series 6 (Box 1211, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Kreuser, Robert J. (Muskego, WI) [file 1/5], 1964-1967; Series 6 (Box 1211, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Kreuser, Robert J. (Muskego, WI) [file 2/5], 1964-1967; Series 6 (Box 1211, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Kreuser, Robert J. (Muskego, WI) [file 3/5], 1964-1967; Series 6 (Box 1211, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Kreuser, Robert J. (Muskego, WI) [file 4/5], 1964-1967; Series 6 (Box 1211, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Kreuser, Robert J. (Muskego, WI) [file 5/5], 1964-1967; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Lalime, Arthur (Darian, CT), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Lee County, IA, 1951; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Lehman, Eugene H., 1957-1958; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Lessard, Alberta (West Allis, WI), 1953-1967; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Ling, Charline v. Puckett, Jim (Chattanooga, TN), 1969; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Littleton, NH, 1969; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Lockport, IL, 1963-1968; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Louisiana State, Mississippi Associations, 1970; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Martinez, Mary, 1974; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-McCramer, Eugene E. (Williamsport, PA), 1966-1968; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-McPherson, Harold (Delray Beach, FL), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Menlo, GA, 1963; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 13)
  - Investigations-Michigan Case, 1961-1962; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 14)
  - Investigations-Miller, Enoch (Fayetteville, AR), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 15)
  - Investigations-Miller, Ronald (Newark, DE), 1963; Series 6 (Box 1212, Folder 16)
  - Investigations-Milwaukee Teachers Association, 1964-1965; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Missoula, Montana Case, 1959-1960; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Mitchell, Blythe C. (Yonkers, NY), 1962; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Mitchell, Mabel M. (Boulder City, NV), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Monson, Cecile (Sioux Falls, SD), 1963-1967; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Morton Salt Company, 1968; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Murphy, Patricia (Moraga, CA), 1970; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Newark, NJ, 1966; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Niagara Falls Teachers Association (Niagara Falls, NY), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-North Carolina Teachers Association (Weldon, NC), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-North Royalton, OH, 1969; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Ohio, 1970; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Oldham County, KY, 1969; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 13)
  - Investigations-Orlans, F. Barbara (Bethesda, MD), 1969; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 14)
  - Investigations-Osmer, Fred v. Hannen, Lew (Durham, NC), 1968; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 15)
  - Investigations-Palm, Inez Eaves (San Antonio, TX), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1213, Folder 16)
  - Investigations-Parker, Ray Elbert (MD), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1214, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Pasadena Education Association, 1961-1962; Series 6 (Box 1214, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Penn-Delco Education Association, 1967; Series 6 (Box 1214, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Pennsylvania State Education Association, 1963; Series 6 (Box 1214, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Pidus, T.P. (Fort Myers, FL) [file 1/2], 1968-1975; Series 6 (Box 1214, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Pidus, T.P. (Fort Myers, FL) [file 2/2], 1968-1975; Series 6 (Box 1214, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Pierre, SD, 1965; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Pinellas and Hillsborough Counties (FL), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Pino, Ed, 1970; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Pinto, Teresa J. (Clinton, IA), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Pitt, Elizabeth J. (Freeport, NY), 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Pittsburgh Inquiry, 1960; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Polk County (FL), 1964-1967; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Pollard, Bascomb J. (Tampa, FL), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Proctor and Gamble Complaint (Crest) [file 1/2], 1965-1972; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Proctor and Gamble Complaint (Crest) [file 2/2], 1965-1972; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Puentes, Robert (Bethpage, NY), 1963; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Quackenbush, Hazel J. (Newark, NJ), 1962; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Rafferty, Max (CA), 1966-1970; Series 6 (Box 1215, Folder 13)
  - Investigations-Renton Education Association (Renton, WA), 1966; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Richmond, VA (Forbes, David), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Rickenbach, Robert (Abington, PA), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Roberts, Richard (Glenview, IL), 1968; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Roberts, Walter E. (Lakeland, FL), 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Rose, Marjorie Anne (Madison, WI), 1971-1972; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Rothenberg, Allen W. (Washington, DC), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Sanich, Rita (El Paso, TX), 1969; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Saunders, Charles [file 1/2], 1970-1972; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Saunders, Charles [file 2/2], 1970-1972; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Saunders v. Burkett [file 1/2], 1970-1971; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Saunders v. Burkett [file 2/2], 1970-1971; Series 6 (Box 1216, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Saunders v. Kelly [file 1/2], 1971; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Saunders v. Kelly [file 2/2], 1971; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Say, John T. (Norfolk, ME), 1968; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Sayre, William R. (Palos Heights, IL), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Schultz, Donald E. (Renton, WA), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Schweiger, Elizabeth L. (Grand Island, NY), 1963-1964; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Scott County, VA, 1964; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Seaber, Ellen (Fort Pierce, FL), 1966; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Seay, Donna (Montgomery, AL), 1963; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Sells, Jake B. (Abingdon, VA), 1962; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Seter, Donald J. (Edwardsville, IL), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-Severson, Arlin (Alamosa, CO), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-Simmons, Thomas (Fairfax, VA), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 13)
  - Investigations-Sinclair, Ernest (Summerville, GA), 1962-1963; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 14)
  - Investigations-Smith, Mortimer, 1964-1966; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 15)
  - Investigations-Sobel, Eleanor (Somerville, MA), 1969; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 16)
  - Investigations-Soley (Racine, WI), 1974-1975; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 17)
  - Investigations-Sorrell, Joy (McKinney, TX), 1969-1971; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 18)
  - Investigations-Springdale, AR, 1962; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 19)
  - Investigations-Stevens Point, WI, 1969; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 20)
  - Investigations-Stirewalt, E.N., 1975; Series 6 (Box 1217, Folder 21)
  - Investigations-Strongville Education Association, 1969; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Sullivan, Bertha E. (Birmingham, AL), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Swearington, Ellis, 1963-1965; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Syracuse, NY, circa 1959; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Taylor, Marshall R. (Wausau, WI), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Teachers National Life Insurance Company, 1967; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Thomas, Charles B. (Festus, MO), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Thompson, R.M. (Storm Lake, IA), 1969; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Tully, William F. (Oswego, NY), 1964; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-UEDA, 1970; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-United Research Associates (OR), 1969; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 11)
  - Investigations-United States History Society (Chicago, IL), 1964-1965; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 12)
  - Investigations-University of California, Los Angeles, 1969; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 13)
  - Investigations-Utah, Salt Lake, 1969; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 14)
  - Investigations-Utah Teachers Situation, 1963-1964; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 15)
  - Investigations-Varnadore, Gary E. (Lancaster, SC), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 16)
  - Investigations-Vellanti, Joseph (Lansing, MI), 1962; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 17)
  - Investigations-Wagner, Thomas (Clark, WY), 1962-1963; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 18)
  - Investigations-Wasielewski, Theodore (Baltimore, MD), 1968; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 19)
  - Investigations-Waukesha, WI, 1961; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 20)
  - Investigations-Weingold, Stanley, 1962; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 21)
  - Investigations-Wendt, Roger (Kalamazoo, MI), 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 22)
  - Investigations-White, Richard (Salt Lake City, UT), 1969; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 23)
  - Investigations-Whitney, Gregory, 1964-1965; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 24)
  - Investigations-Wichita, KS (Debbrecht, W.L.), 1963-1964; Series 6 (Box 1218, Folder 25)
  - Investigations-Wichita City Teachers Association (Wichita, KS), 1961-1962; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 1)
  - Investigations-Wilbur, Lee H. (Stafford Springs, CT), 1964; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 2)
  - Investigations-Wilkerson, Gaynor M. (Maxton, NC), 1961; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 3)
  - Investigations-Williams, Arizona (Pettengill, Robert C.), 1965; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 4)
  - Investigations-Wilson, Helen Joyce (Todd County, KY), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 5)
  - Investigations-Winnebago, NE (Eugene Geister), 1965-1969; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 6)
  - Investigations-Wisconsin Education Association (Rochschild-Schofield Area), 1966-1967; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 7)
  - Investigations-Worland, WY, 1959; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 8)
  - Investigations-Wright, Erwin U. (Radford, VA), 1969; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 9)
  - Investigations-Young, Jeannine Hill (Houston, TX), 1964; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 10)
  - Investigations-Zafiran, James (Bowling Green, OH), 1967; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 11)
  - Judicial Board, 1972; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 12)
  - Kinley, F. Stuart, 1972; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 13)
  - Legal Brief-Herndon and Ryor v. Pasternak, Santangelo, Urick and McDonald [file 1/2], 1972-1973; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 14)
  - Legal Brief-Herndon and Ryor v. Pasternak, Santangelo, Urick and McDonald [file 2/2], 1972-1973; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 15)
  - Legal Brief-Saunders v. Burkett, July 1971-August 1971; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 16)
  - Legal Brief-Saunders v. Kelly, May 1971-June 1971; Series 6 (Box 1219, Folder 17)
  - Mailings about National Conference on Ethics, September 1967-November 1967; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 1)
  - Materials Sent to Committee Members, 1963-1975; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 2)
  - McKay, Vera B., 1972; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 3)
  - Medical Discipline, 1962; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 4)
  - Medical Profession, 1959; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 5)
  - Meeting (Fort Worth, TX), February 1968-May 1968; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 6)
  - Meeting (Washington, DC), October 1966-February 1967; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 7)
  - Meeting (Washington, DC), January 1968; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 8)
  - Meeting (Washington, DC), February 1968-March 1968; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, February 1967; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, October 1968-November 1970; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, October 1971-June 1974; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 12)
  - Minutes, October 1972; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 13)
  - Moral Turpitude Cases, 1965; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 14)
  - Motion Passed by 1962 Delegate Assembly for Implementation of Proposed New Code of Ethics, Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 15)
  - National Alliance of Black School Educators, 1975; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 16)
  - NEA Convention (Minneapolis, MN), May 1967-July 1967; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 17)
  - New Code of Ethics-Compliments and Criticisms, April 1963-July 1968; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 18)
  - New Publication on Code of Ethics, March 1969-April 1969; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 19)
  - New Publication on "The Code of Ethics and the Local Education Association", January 1969; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 20)
  - New Publication on "Enforcement Procedures and Conduct of Hearing", 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 21)
  - New Publication on "Opinions", 1968-1969; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 22)
  - NLRB Procedures, circa 1972; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 23)
  - Oath of Pledge for Teachers, 1949-1952; Series 6 (Box 1220, Folder 24)
  - Opinion 1, 1951; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 1)
  - Opinion 2, 1951; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 2)
  - Opinion 3, 1952; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 3)
  - Opinion 4, 1951-1968; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 4)
  - Opinion 5, 1953; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 5)
  - Opinion 6, 1953; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 6)
  - Opinion 7, 1953; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 7)
  - Opinion 8, 1953; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 8)
  - Opinion 9, 1953; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 9)
  - Opinion 10, 1953; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 10)
  - Opinion 11, 1953; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 11)
  - Opinion 12, 1954; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 12)
  - Opinion 13, 1954; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 13)
  - Opinion 14, 1954; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 14)
  - Opinion 15, 1954; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 15)
  - Opinion 16, 1954; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 16)
  - Opinion 17, 1954; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 17)
  - Opinion 18, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 18)
  - Opinion 19, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 19)
  - Opinion 20, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 20)
  - Opinion 21, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 21)
  - Opinion 22, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 22)
  - Opinion 23, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 23)
  - Opinion 24, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 24)
  - Opinion 25, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 25)
  - Opinion 26, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 26)
  - Opinion 27, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 27)
  - Opinion 28, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 28)
  - Opinion 29, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 29)
  - Opinion 30, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 30)
  - Opinion 31, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 31)
  - Opinion 32, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 32)
  - Opinion 33, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 33)
  - Opinion 34, 1955; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 34)
  - Opinion 35, 1956; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 35)
  - Opinion 36, 1957; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 36)
  - Opinion 37, 1958; Series 6 (Box 1221, Folder 37)
  - Opinion 38, 1959; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 1)
  - Opinion 39, 1959; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 2)
  - Opinion 40, 1960; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 3)
  - Opinion 41, 1961-1969; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 4)
  - Opinion 42, 1961; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 5)
  - Opinion 43, 1963; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 6)
  - Opinion 44, 1963-1964; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 7)
  - Opinion 45, 1964; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 8)
  - Opinion 46, 1964; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 9)
  - Opinion 47, 1964; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 10)
  - Opinion 48, 1964; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 11)
  - Opinion 49, 1963-1965; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 12)
  - Opinion 50, 1966; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 13)
  - Opinion 51, 1966; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 14)
  - Opinion 52, 1968; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 15)
  - Opinion 53, 1967; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 16)
  - Opinion-Encyclopedia Britannica, 1965; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 17)
  - Opinion-General File, 1966-1967; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 18)
  - Opinion-Requests for, 1965-1969; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 19)
  - Opinion-Set of Printed Opinions 1-32, 1952-1955; Series 6 (Box 1222, Folder 20)
  - Opinion-Strikes By Teachers, 1965-1966; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 1)
  - "Opinions of the Committee on Professional Ethics", 1950; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 2)
  - "Opinions of the Committee on Professional Ethics", 1955; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 3)
  - "Opinions of the Committee on Professional Ethics", 1958; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 4)
  - "Opinions of the Committee on Professional Ethics", 1960; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 5)
  - Opinions of the Committee on Professional Ethics, June 1960; series 6 (Box 4400, Folder 11)
  - "Opinions of the Committee on Professional Ethics", 1964; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 6)
  - "Opinions of the Committee on Professional Ethics", 1966; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 7)
  - "Opinions of the Committee on Professional Ethics", 1969; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 8)
  - Opinions of the Ethics Committee [file 1/2], September 1967-April 1969; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 9)
  - Opinions of the Ethics Committee [file 2/2], September 1967-April 1969; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 10)
  - Opinion of Koeller v. Kreuser Case, December 1966; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 11)
  - ORC Public Opinion Index, October 1973; Series 6 (Box 1223, Folder 12)
  - Originals, 1974; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 1)
  - Paul Smith Case, 1970-1973; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 2)
  - Pictures Taken at National Conference on Ethics, 1962-1963; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 3)
    Contains 10 photos and 43 negatives.
  - Possible Future Cases, 1967-1968; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 4)
  - Possible Future Cases, 1969; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 5)
  - Possible Future Cases, 1970; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 6)
  - Presentation to NEA Executive Committee, 1970; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 7)
  - Procedures for Enforcement of the Code of Ethics, October 1966; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 8)
  - Professional Codes of Ethics [file 1/2], 1965-1974; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 9)
  - Professional Codes of Ethics [file 2/2], 1965-1974; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Code of Ethics Copies Sent to Educational Writers and Other Individuals, October 1961-October 1962; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Special Project to Develop Basic Code of Ethics, 1963; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 12)
  - Publications, 1952-1963; Series 6 (Box 1521, Folder 2)
  - Publications-The Challenge, April 1963; Series 6 (Box 1224, Folder 13)
  - Publications-"A Class in the Day of Mr. Misanthrope", June 1963; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 1)
  - Publications-"The Code of Ethics for the Education Profession", February 1963; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 2)
  - Publications-"A Code of Ethics for the Education Profession", 1934; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 3)
  - Publications-"The Code of Ethics for the Education Profession", July 1963; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 4)
  - Publications-"Code of Ethics of the Education Profession", 1968-1972; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 5)
  - Publications-"Code of Ethics of the Education Profession", 1975; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 6)
  - Publications-"The Code of Ethics of the Education Profession, A Re-Examination", November 1966; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 7)
  - Publications-"Code of Ethics of the NEA of the United States", 1952; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 8)
  - Publications-"Do You Know Liz?", July 1953; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 9)
  - Publications-"Enforcement of the Code of Ethics of the Education Profession", 1969; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 10)
  - Publications-"Enforcement of the Code of Ethics of the Education Profession", 1973; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 11)
  - Publications-"Ethics Materials Available from State Associations", June 1958; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 12)
  - Publications-Guides for Ethics Committees-Local Education Association, January 1960; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 13)
  - Publications-"Implementing the Code of Ethics of the Education Profession and Strengthening Professional Rights", June 1964; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 14)
  - Publications-"Interpretations of the Code of Ethics", December 1963; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 15)
  - Publications-"A Method of Teaching Professional Ethics", February 1959; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 16)
  - Publications-"National Conference on Proposed Code of Ethics for the Education Profession", November 1962; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 17)
  - Publications-"A Preliminary Guideline for Implementing the Code and Strengthening Professional Rights", 1963; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 18)
  - Publications-"Professional Ethics and Continuing Teacher Licensure", October 1971; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 19)
  - Publications-"Professional Ethics in the Preparation of Teachers", April 1949; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 20)
  - Publications-Professional Ethics Quiz, December 1959; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 21)
  - Publications-Professional Ethics, A Unit of Work, October 1951; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 22)
  - Publications-"A Proposed Basic Code of Ethics for the Education Profession", July 1962-October 1962; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 23)
  - Publications-"Proposed Revision of the Code of Ethics of the Education Profession", 1974; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 24)
  - Publications-"Protecting the Profession's Interest in Ethical Conduct", September 1970; Series 6 (Box 1225, Folder 25)